

KATIE FULLMER designer & developer



ABOUT

I have worked in the web design and development space for over a decade, and have continually broadened my skillsets over that time. My specialty is designing and developing custom websites and applications, utilizing a wide range of technologies while delivering custom interfaces that focus on user experience, performance, and functionality. I also have extensive experience in designing ads for print and online use.

This industry is constantly evolving, so I make it a priority to stay at the forefront of the web technology and standards. One of my favorite aspects of web design and development is the opportunity for creative problem-solving—I love taking on new challenges with each project and seeing the end result come to fruition.



CONTACT

☑ katiegfullmer@gmail.com

www.katiefullmer.com



EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF FINE ARTS / AUG 2008 - MAY 2012

College of Art & Design - Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana

ART HISTORY MINOR DEGREE / AUG 2008 - MAY 2012

College of Art & Design - Louisiana State University Baton Rouge, Louisiana



EXPERIENCE

HEALTH CONNECTIVE / JUN 2012 - PRESENT

Senior Designer & Front End Developer in New Orleans, LA Provide custom web design and application development, as well as online and print advertising for clients.

BEACHVIEW ENERGY / AUG 2017 - FEB 2020

Freelance Graphic Designer in Brunswick, GA Provide quarterly customer newsletter layout and design, branding and

Provide quarterly customer newsletter layout and design, branding and promotional design services.

UTILITY SERVICES - POWER SECURE / JUL 2012 - AUG 2018

Freelance Graphic Designer in Atlanta, GA

Design the company-wide, quaterly newsletter along with a monthly newsletter for the Utility Services division along with other promtional materials.

AMERICAN ALL STAR / MAY 2008 - MAY 2017

Freelance Designer, Camp Director & Dance Instructor in Mandeville, LA Design all promotional media such as brochures, t-shirts, informational binders, & folders.

DIG MAGAZINE / AUG 2011 - JUN 2012

Graphic Designer in Baton Rouge, LA

Design various medias on strict deadlines such as advertisements, posters, media kits, identities, & layouts.

LSU ITS / JAN 2009 - AUG 2011

Information Technology Services Student Worker in Baton Rouge, LA



AFFILIATIONS

AIGA / 2011 - PRESENT Professional Association for Design

DELTA DELTA / 2009 - 2012

Order of Omega

GDSA / 2009 - 2012 LSU Graphic Design Student Association